Guide to the Michael H. Nee clippings collection, 1973-1991.
Nee, Michael H. clippings collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Michael H. Nee clippings collection, 1973-1991.
7785
Nee, Michael H.
1.3 cubic ft.
Newsclippings
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
A collection of clippings documenting anything related to gay people.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
A collection of clippings documenting anything related to gay people, mostly from Madison, Wisconsin newspapers for 1978-1979 and mostly from Chicago newspapers for 1980-1991. Plus photographs of gay softball teams and pride parades in Chicago in 1981 and correspondence to public officials and others about gay issues.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Nee, Michael H.
Subjects:
Gays.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Collecting program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- Gay Organization Materials and Newsletters
  - Greater Chicago Gay and Lesbian Democrats, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Gay Horizons, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gay Academic Union Chicago Chapter, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Gay and Lesbian History Project, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The United, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Gay Madison"-The United newsletter, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GATES and NOGLSTP newsletters: societies of gay technicians, engineers and scientists, 1982-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Windy City Athletic Association, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Various Chicago gay organizations, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Illinois Gay and Lesbian Task Force, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - University of Wisconsin- Milwaukee: Gay Community (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Renaissance Newsletter, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Humboldt Society: Lesbian and Gay Naturalist of Philadelphia, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bronx: Lesbian and Gay Independent Democrats, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Natural History, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - GLAD: Gay and Lesbian Advocates and Defenders, Inc., 1981-1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - NGLTF (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "It's Time" and "The Task Force Report"- NGLTF newsletters, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Social Action Training Group (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Gay Community News (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Various national gay organizations (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Political Activism
  - Political Activism (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Government and Legislative information, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Legislator candidates, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Madison Committee for Gay Rights (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "A Gay and Lesbian Agenda for Chicago", June 1983 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - National Day of Lesbian and Gay Resistance/Roll Back Reaganism march flyer (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - ACT UP Mailing, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Illinois Lesbian and Gay Student Caucus, April 13-14, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Activist pamphlets, 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - New York activism (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Michael Nee correspondence, 1973-1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Gay Life
  - "Fairie"- Harry Hay speech at Colorado Fairie Circle, August 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - "The Gays and the Police"- Chicago Police Department training bulletin, April 13, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Sexual Health information (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Homosexuality and Christianity, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Map of gay life in Chicago (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Flyers for Chicago queer plays (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - International Mr. Leather flyer (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Chicago Gay events, 1981-1988 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 1981 Chicago Directory: A Gay Guide to Businesses and Entertainment, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Journey Womyn: "The Catalyst", April 1981 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Gaylife: Chicago's Gay and Lesbian Newsweekly, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Outlines: The Voice of the Gay and Lesbian Community, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - A Gay Bibliography, January 1978, March 1984 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - "America Now: Why the Gays Came Out of the Closet", 1981 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Newspaper and Magazine articles, 1978-1987 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - "Genetic evidence for different male and female roles during cultural transitions in the British Isles", April 24, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Chicago-Illinois Pride Parade photo album, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Gay Softball Teams photo album, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Collection of Newspaper Clippings
  - Collection introduction by Michael Nee, 1973-1977 Clippings, 2013, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - 1978 Clippings, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - 1979-1980 Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 1981-1982 Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - 1983 Clippings, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1984 Clippings, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1987-1991 Clippings, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Loose Clippings, 1978-2006 (Box 2, Folder 4)